AI videos are about to break the
Cling 3.0 即将让 AI 视频风靡
internet with Cling 3.0 because now you
网络，因为现在你
can literally make the most realistic
可以制作出最逼真的
videos with some of the best lip syncs
视频，并拥有我们见过的最好的唇形同步效果
we've ever seen. And trust me when I say
。 相信我
this, but we've got some wild stuff to
，我们有一些精彩的内容要
show you because you can literally
展示给你，因为你真的可以
create some dynamic videos like this
制作出一些像这个
absolutely crazy basketball video. Or
绝对疯狂的篮球视频一样充满活力的视频。 或者
you can do movie like scenes like this
你可以制作类似电影的场景，像这样
where it continuously transitions to the
不断过渡到
next sequence. Or how about create a
下一个场景。 或者，何不创作一个
full-on fight scene like this one? or
像这样的完整打斗场景呢？ 甚至可以
even create multi character talking
创作像这样的多角色对话
scenes like this, which is absolutely
场景，这简直太
wild. Now, a lot of creators are making
疯狂了。 现在，很多创作者都在制作
videos about the Cling 3.0 update, but
关于 Cling 3.0 更新的视频，但
they aren't actually showing you the
他们实际上并没有向你展示
best ways to use it, which is what we're
使用它的最佳方法，而这正是我们
going to be doing in this video. So,
将在本视频中要做的。 所以，
this is going to be the only guide
这将是
you're going to need to use Cling
你使用 Cling
[music] 3.0. And on top of this, I'm
[音乐] 3.0 所需的唯一指南。 除此之外，我
going to be sharing two super useful
还会分享两个超级实用的
custom GPTs [music]
自定义 GPT（音乐），
to help you prompt your images and
帮助你为图片和视频添加提示
videos, just so you can get the best
，这样你就能轻松获得最佳
prompts super easily without wasting any
提示，而不会浪费任何
credits. Now, at a high level, Cling 3.0
积分。 现在，从宏观层面来看，Cling 3.0
is now a unified video generation model
已经是一个统一的视频生成模型，
that has enhanced audio generations,
它增强了音频生成、
multi-shot narratives, [music]
多镜头叙事、[音乐]
directional physics, native cinematic
方向性物理效果、原生电影
workflows, and on top of all of that,
工作流程，除此之外，
you now have 15-second video
它还支持 15 秒视频
generations, and the [music] best
生成，并且拥有我们迄今为止见过的最好的[音乐]
subject consistency we've seen so far.
主题一致性。
Now, I'm also going to show you some
现在，我还要向你展示一些
stuff no one else is talking about, like
其他人没有谈到的东西，比如
how you can actually go ahead and
如何重新
relight your videos, swap out objects,
打光你的视频、替换物体、
refframe compositions, and even clean up
重新构图，甚至清理
your videos. So, it's safe to say
你的视频。 所以，可以说
there's a lot to cover in this video, so
这段视频的内容非常丰富，请做好准备
strap in. And of course, before we jump
。当然，在深入
into all of it, if you are new to AI and
探讨所有内容之前，如果您是人工智能新手，
want to learn how to master all the best
想要学习如何掌握所有最佳
AI tools to create content for yourself
人工智能工具来为自己
or your brand, or you just want to stay
或品牌创作内容，或者您​​只是想保持
ahead of the curve, then be sure to
领先地位，那么请务必
check out my AI community down below.
查看下方我的人工智能社区。
With all that said, let's go ahead and
说了这么多，我们就
jump right into it. Okay, so to recap, I
直接进入正题吧。 好的，总结一下，我
want to quickly show you a fun 30-cond
想快速地向大家展示一段
video we made for the launch of Cling
我们为 Cling 3.0 发布而制作的有趣的 30 秒视频，
3.0 highlighting its core new features
重点介绍其核心新功能，
just so you can kind of see the proof in
以便大家能够亲眼见证其效果
the pudding. So, let's go ahead and give
。 那么，我们
it a quick watch. All right, listen up
快速浏览一下吧。 好了，各位笨蛋们，听好了，
made now because Cling 3.0 can generate
现在电影就是这样拍出来的，因为 Cling 3.0 可以
multi-shot scenes in one go.
一次性生成多镜头场景。
&gt;&gt; Wait, so you're telling me this is from
等等，你是说这
just one image?
仅仅是一张图片的结果？
&gt;&gt; Guys, come on. I don't have all day. You
伙计们，拜托。 我没那么多时间。 你
can even lock characters and objects so
甚至可以锁定角色和对象，使
everything stays consistent, even the
所有内容保持一致，包括
text.
文本。
&gt;&gt; Oh, and did I mention you now get
哦，对了，我有没有提到现在你可以看到
&gt;&gt; with multiple characters in the same
同一场景中出现多个角色的 15 秒视频
scene?
？
&gt;&gt; Mhm.
嗯。
&gt;&gt; even across different languages.
即使使用不同的语言，Clling 也能准确地知道是谁在说话。
&gt;&gt; Okay, that was pretty epic, right? But
好吧，那真是太精彩了，对吧？ 但是，
how exactly can you go ahead and
究竟该如何才能像这样重新
recreate videos just like [music] this?
制作视频呢？
Well, jumping right into it, we can
好，我们直接进入正题，我们可以通过
access Clling a few different ways, but
几种不同的方式访问 Clling，但
inside of Hicksfield for a few big
出于几个
reasons. Well, the first one is pricing
主要原因，我们将在 Hicksfield 中通过音乐来使用它。 首先是价格，
because they're currently running some
因为他们目前正在进行一些
pretty crazy deals at the moment where
非常划算的促销活动，
you can get unlimited generations for a
你可以以非常优惠的价格获得无限代数的服务
crazy good price. And you're also
。 而且您还
getting access to all the leading image
可以使用所有领先的图像
and video models. So, it's basically a
和视频模型。 所以，这基本上是
no-brainer. So, if you do want to check
显而易见的。 所以，如果您想查看一下
it out, we'll leave a link to that in
，我们会在描述中留下链接
the description. But to use Clling, it's
。 但使用 Cling
actually pretty easy. Once you're on the
其实非常简单。 进入
Higsfield main page, you can hover over
Higsfield 主页后，您可以将鼠标悬停在
to video. Now, depending on when you're
视频上。 现在，根据您
actually watching this video, it might
观看此视频的时间，它可能会
appear up here. But for now, we have
出现在这里。 但目前我们只有
Cling 2.6 because we're in early access.
Cling 2.6 版本，因为我们还处于抢先体验阶段。
But worry not, because if you just go
但别担心，只要你
ahead and click on that, you can access
点击它，就可以通过
it a few different ways. One by either
几种不同的方式访问它。 一种方法是
clicking on model, then hover over to
点击模型，然后将鼠标悬停在
Cling, and then you'll see you got three
Cling 上，然后您会看到三个
new options. Cling 3.0, Cling 3.0 Omni,
新选项。  Cling 3.0、Cling 3.0 Omni，
and then Cling 3.0. So, we're going to
然后是 Cling 3.0。 所以，我们将从
start off with Cling 3.0, O and then
Cling 3.0 开始，然后再
we'll jump into the other ones. Again,
深入研究其他版本。
you can also access it. If you click on
您也可以访问它。 如果您点击
change here, you should see link here.
这里的更改，您应该会看到这里的链接。
Then go ahead and click on general. Now,
然后点击“常规”。
if you're not too familiar with video
如果您对视频模型不太熟悉
models, let's quickly go over the
，我们快速浏览一下
settings. Here we've got our start and
设置。 这里是起始帧和
end frames. This is basically where you
结束帧。 这里基本上
can input images. Down here, we have our
可以输入图片。 下面是我们的具体
description. Then we've got our model,
描述。 然后我们就有了模型和
our duration, and like we said, we can
持续时间，就像我们说的那样，现在我们可以
now bump it up to 15 seconds. You will
把它增加到 15 秒。 你会
see here because we're in early access,
发现，由于我们目前处于抢先体验阶段，所以
we have longer wait times, but by the
等待时间较长，但据 Clling 和 Higs 本人透露，到
10th of February, this will have sped up
2 月 10 日，等待时间将会大幅缩短
Clling and by Higs themselves. So that's
。
awesome. Here you can change your aspect
太棒了。 在这里您可以更改
ratio, 16x9, 9x6, and 1x1. And then, of
宽高比，16:9、9:6 和 1:1。 当然，还有
course, you have your resolution. Now,
你的新年决心。 现在，
Cling 3.0 compared to Cling 2.6, and
Cling 3.0 与 Cling 2.6 相比有三个主要区别，
that is that you have native audio
其中之一是视频中内置了原生音频
inside of your videos. can disable it if
。 如果你愿意，可以禁用它，
you want, but I don't really see why you
但我不太明白你为什么要
would want to disable it. You then have
禁用它。 接下来是
your multi-shots, which is an absolute
多重射击，这绝对是
gamecher, and we're going to cover this
制胜法宝，我们马上就来介绍一下
in just a minute. Then we also have
。 此外，我们还有
elements, which is by far one of the
元素功能，这绝对是
most underrated features inside of Cling
Cling 3.0 中最被低估的功能之一
3.0. No one's talking about it, but if
。 虽然没人谈论这件事，但如果
you want realistic cinematic looking
你想要制作出画面逼真、风格一致的电影级
videos with consistency, you need to be
视频，你就需要
using elements. Okay, so let's start off
使用各种元素。 好的，那么让我们
by creating our very first multi-shot
从创建第一个多镜头
video as that's the most complex part of
视频开始，因为这是新模型中最复杂的部分
the new model, but it doesn't actually
，但实际上并不
need to be that complex. We're going to
需要那么复杂。 我们将先
cover the simple method and then we'll
介绍简单的方法，然后再
move over to the more complex. So, let's
介绍更复杂的方法。 那么，我们就从
go ahead and start off with this image
这张照片开始吧
right here, which is a super cool image
，这是一张
of me riding a horse with a cowboy hat.
我戴着牛仔帽骑马的超酷照片。
Um, and I think it looks awesome. It's
嗯，我觉得它看起来棒极了。 它
got some really like nostalgic looks,
看起来真的很有怀旧感，
like it's got like that noise in the
就像背景里有那种噪音
background, a little bit of a blur to
，还有点模糊的效果
it. I really like it. So, what we're
。 我非常喜欢它。 所以，接下来我们要做的就是把它
just drag that in right here. Now, from
拖到这里来。 接下来
here, we're going to go ahead and enable
，我们将启用
multi-shot. Now, you'll see you have a
多重拍摄功能。 现在，你会看到有
bunch of different options, but you
很多不同的选项，但你
basically kind of want to decide right
基本上需要一开始就决定
off the bat how many shots you want. You
你想拍多少张照片。 您
can go ahead and click on add shot here,
可以点击这里的“添加照片”，
and it'll add a second shot. Now, you
它会添加第二张照片。 现在，
can add up to six shots, I believe. Um,
我相信最多可以添加六次射击。 嗯，
or it is six shots if you bring it down
或者说，如果把
to 2 seconds per shot. But for the
每次射击时间缩短到 2 秒，那就是 6 次射击。 但就本次拍摄
purposes of this, we're going to go
而言，我们将
ahead and delete these because we want
删除这些照片，因为我们需要
three different shots. So, like I said,
三张不同的照片。 所以，就像我说的，
you can take it the simple route or the
你可以选择简单的方法，也可以选择
more complex route, but we're actually
更复杂的方法，但我们现在要
going to go ahead and start inputting
开始输入
our prompts. So, the first one we're
提示了。 所以，我们要用的第一个例子
going to use is super simple and it's
非常简单，就是
just going to be man says in brackets
男人在括号里说
Hollywood is officially cooked. The
好莱坞正式完蛋了。
second shot is going to be change angle
第二个镜头将改变角度，
to side profile and man says because now
改为侧面轮廓，因为现在
you can have multi-shot videos. Now, for
你可以拍摄多镜头视频了。 接下来，拍摄
the third shot, we're then going to
第三张照片时，我们将
change the angle again to a front
再次改变角度，拍摄
closeup of the man. And he says from a
男子的正面特写。 他说，这一切都源于
single image. And that's it. That's all
一张图片。 就这样。
you have to do. You don't have to do any
你只需要做这些。 您无需像右侧所示那样进行任何
complicated prompting like you can see
复杂的提示
on the right here. You can do it super
。 你可以用非常
simply. Go ahead and hit on generate and
简单的方法做到。 点击生成按钮，即可
then you get a video. Now, I actually
获得一段视频。 实际上，我
skipped a step and that is changing the
跳过了一个步骤，那就是更改
duration of your video. Now, it doesn't
视频时长。 其实，
actually matter too much when you're
当你
doing multi-shots because Cling actually
进行多图拼接时，这并不太重要，因为 Cling
analyzes your text anyway. So, it kind
无论如何都会分析你的文本。 所以，它大概能
of understands when it needs to change
判断什么时候需要换
shots. But if you do want to change your
镜头。 但如果你确实想改变你的
shots and have your timings exactly how
投篮动作，并且希望投篮时机完全按照现在的节奏来，
it is and you're not too sure, just kind
但你又不太确定，那就大声把
of say the sentences out loud. So,
这些句子说出来。 所以，
Hollywood [music] is officially cooked.
好莱坞音乐界正式完蛋了。
So, that's about 4 seconds. For the
所以，大概是4秒钟。
second shot, because now you have
第二个镜头，因为现在你有了
multiple shot videos, that's about 3
多镜头视频，大约需要 3
seconds. And then from a single image,
秒钟。 然后，从单张图片来看，大约需要
that's about 2 seconds. So, that works
2 秒钟。 所以，效果
pretty well. Hollywood is officially
相当不错。 好莱坞彻底
cooked because now you can have
完蛋了，因为现在你可以用
multi-shot videos from [music] a single
一张图片制作多镜头音乐视频
image.
。
&gt;&gt; Okay, so now moving on to more complex
好的，现在我们来学习更复杂的
multi-shots. Let's go ahead and play
多重拍摄。 我们现在就播放
this video right here and I'll show you
这段视频，我会向你展示
exactly how you can recreate [music] it
如何重现[音乐]，
&gt;&gt; because Cling 3.0 can generate
因为 Cling 3.0 可以
multi-shot scenes in one go.
一次性生成多镜头场景。
&gt;&gt; Wait, so you're telling me this is from
等等，你是说这
just one image?
仅仅是一张图片的结果？
&gt;&gt; Guys, come on. I don't have all day.
伙计们，拜托。 我没那么多时间。   那真是
&gt;&gt; So, that was pretty cool. And there's a
太棒了。 这里面有很多
the scenes, but once you understand it,
幕后运作，但一旦你理解了，就会发现
it's not complicated whatsoever. So, the
其实一点也不复杂。 所以，
core features that we're actually going
我们实际要使用的核心功能
to be using is a first frame,
是第一帧、
multi-shot, and then [music] elements.
多镜头，然后是[音乐]元素。
So, we're going to start off by dragging
所以，我们首先要像这样拖入
in our first frame just like this. Now,
第一帧。 现在，
we're going to go ahead and add three
我们将再增加三个
more shots because we had a free shot
镜头，因为我们有一次免费拍摄的
sequence. And now, I've gone ahead and
机会。 现在，我已经
added in my prompt. So, for the first
添加了我的提示。 所以，第一个
shot, we've got a windy day on the
镜头展现的是山上刮风的一天，
mountain in because we're describing the
因为我们正在描述
background that we have or the
我们所处的背景或
environment. We've got mail lead says
环境。 我们有邮件线索，邮件负责人
with irreressible smile because clink
笑着说，因为 clink
3.0 can generate multi-shot scenes in
3.0 可以一次性生成多镜头场景
one go. So, we're describing the scene
。 所以，我们现在要描述一下当时的场景
here. We've got this at mail says and
。 邮件里是这样写的，
then we have the sentence that we want
然后我们还有我们
to say. Now the reason we have the at
想说的句子。 现在我们之所以有
mail is I'll explain it in just a moment
@mail，我稍后会解释，
but I do want to quickly go through the
但我想先快速浏览一下
prompts just so you guys can understand.
提示，以便你们能够理解。
Um here for the second shot again we're
嗯，这里是第二个镜头，我们再次
describing the camera movement that we
描述我们
want it to change too. And then it
希望它改变的摄像机运动。 然后，它
reveals the second character which is
揭晓了第二个角色，那就是
the Margot Robbie. And then she says,
玛格特·罗比。 然后她说：
"Wait, you're telling me this is just
“等等，你是说这只是
from one image." And then we're keeping
一张图片而已。” 然后我们在
a little bit more consistency here,
这里保持一些一致性，
keeping it cinematic quality and
保持电影般的画质和
handheld camera feel. For the third
手持摄影机的感觉。 第三个
shot, we've got pans back to at Deadpool
镜头，镜头摇回到死侍身上，他
saying, "Guys, come on. I don't have all
说道：“伙计们，拜托。我没时间陪你们玩
day." Now, the reason why we're adding
。” 现在，我们之所以要添加
the at male lead and the at female lead
男主角和女主角，
is because we're actually going to be
是因为我们实际上要
using elements. So, we can go ahead and
使用一些元素。 所以，我们可以把
remove this. But you can see as soon as
它删除。 但是你可以看到，
I add an at, you can see I've got start
我一加上 at，你就可以看到我有了起始
frame, then we got Seb, then I've got
帧，然后是 Seb，然后是
Marot. So, because we actually see
Marot。 所以，因为我们实际上在
everyone here, we can actually keep at
这里看到了每个人，我们实际上可以保持在
start frame, but then we can say at Seb
起始帧，但然后我们可以说，塞巴斯蒂安
says with an universal smile blah blah
带着普遍的微笑说，等等
blah. So, if we go ahead and click on
等等。 所以，如果我们点击
elements here, you can see these are the
这里的元素，您可以看到这些是
elements that I've created. So, we've
我创建的元素。 所以，我们给
got one for Seb and we've got one for
塞巴斯蒂安准备了一份，也给
Mark. Now, to create elements, it's
马克准备了一份。 现在，创建元素
super simple. All you need to do is go
非常简单。 你只需要把
characters that you want. So, we've got
你想要的角色图片拖进去就行了。 所以，我们有
this image and this image of me, which
这张图片，还有这张我的照片，
we can go ahead and bring in just like
我们可以像这样把它导入进来
this. And you can go ahead and add up to
。 你还可以再添加最多
two more images, but for me, this works
两张图片，但对我来说，这样就
perfect. We can then go ahead and give
足够了。 然后我们就可以给
it a name like Seb. And if you don't
它取个名字，比如塞巴斯蒂安。 如果你不想
yourself, what you can actually go ahead
自己描述，你可以
and do is basically add in your images
做的就是添加图片，然后
and just say briefly describe the man in
简要描述一下图片中的人
this image. Go ahead and copy that. Then
。 请复制这段文字。 然后
you can go ahead and paste that in just
你就可以像
like that. Then you can go ahead and
这样粘贴进去了。 然后你可以
click on generate [music] and then it'll
点击生成[音乐]，它就会
create your characters like this. Now
像这样创建你的角色。
the reason why you're creating your
你创建这些
elements is to basically create multiple
元素的原因基本上是为了创建多个
different shots. So I'd recommend having
不同的镜头。 所以我建议
profile if you can because we've done
你最好准备一张特写、一张全身照和一张侧面照，因为我们进行了
extensive testing and those are the most
大量的测试，这些是最
important ones that you want to be
重要的照片，你应该多多
using. Now quick tip for you. If you
使用。 现在给你一个小提示。 如果你
want to do this super easily, let me
想轻松完成这项操作，让我
quickly walk you through a little bit of
快速地带你了解一下具体步骤
a work. So we head over to Nana Banana
。 于是我们前往Nana Banana
Pro. You can see we've got a bunch of
Pro。 你可以看到我们有很多
different images, which is awesome. If
不同的图片，这太棒了。 如果
we scroll down here, you can see we've
我们向下滚动，可以看到我们已经
got our master image. Now, to create
有了主图像。 创建
this master image was pretty simple. We
这个主镜像非常简单。 我们
said combine character one and character
说要把角色一和角色
2 [music] in the same environment and
二（音乐）放在同一个环境中，让
have Deadpool as the wedding officient.
死侍担任婚礼司仪。
So, this was our final image, which is
所以，这就是我们的最终图像，
now our start frame. And you can see
现在它成为了我们的起始帧。 你可以看到，
that the images that I used was this one
我使用的图片就是这张
of me. So, it was like a sideby-side
我的照片。 所以，这就像是并排
shot. And then the one for Margo was a
拍摄一样。 然后，给玛戈做的那件是
3x3 one just because the dress is a
3x3 的，因为她的裙子比较
little bit more complicated. So we
复杂。 所以我们
wanted to add the details. So the prompt
想补充一些细节。 所以，
that we used for this was basically um
我们用来做这件事的提示基本上就是……
this entire thing. I won't read it but
整个过程。 我不会仔细阅读，但
I'll scroll down just so you can
我会向下滚动，让你
basically get an understanding. Don't
大致了解一下。 别
believe we used any reference images at
以为我们完全没用任何参考图片，
all because you know Margot Robbie is
因为你知道玛格特·罗比是
quite an iconic character. They already
一个非常标志性的人物。 他们已经
have a lot of data on this person. But
掌握了关于这个人的很多数据。 但
we did the exact same thing with the
我们用
photo of me, but we used reference
我的照片也做了同样的事情，只不过我们使用了参考
images to create this right here. Here
图片来创作出现在这个作品。 这里
you can see we've got this reference
你可以看到，我们有一张参考
image which I found online. And then all
图片，是我在网上找到的。 然后
I did was then add this picture of me.
我所做的就是上传了这张我的照片。
And then I just said uh take the framing
然后我就说，呃，按照
and start from image one and replace the
第一张图片的构图，把图片中的人换成
man uh to be the one from image two,
第二张图片中的人，
which then gave us this shot. And you
这样就得到了这张照片。 你
can see that I did a few generations uh
可以看到我做了几代修改，
modified the prompt slightly to make it
稍微修改了一下提示，让它
look a little better. Then we had this
看起来更好一些。 然后我们就形成了这种
consistent style across the board which
统一的风格，
then generated this image right here.
最终就形成了现在我们看到的这幅图像。
Now once you have this again you can
现在，有了它，您就可以
create multiple angles by using similar
使用类似的提示创建多个角度，
prompts like this where you can create
例如创建
side profiles or what you can go ahead
侧面轮廓，或者您可以
and do is click on add and then you can
点击添加，然后
use the angles 2.0. Now angles 2.0 is
使用角度 2.0。 现在 Angles 2.0
super awesome because you can add your
非常棒，因为你可以像这样添加你的
base image like this and then you can go
基础图像，然后你可以
ahead and click on this button right
点击这里的这个按钮
here. Generate from 12 best angles.
。 从 12 个最佳角度生成图像。
[music] You hit generate. It only costs
[音乐] 你按下了生成键。 只需花费
2.4 full credits and then you get a
2.4 个完整积分，你就
bunch of different angles that you can
可以立即获得许多不同的角度，而
use right off the bat without having
无需
prompt. So coming back to the multi-shot
提示。 现在回到多镜头
sequence. I know this was a bit of a
序列。 我知道这篇文章有点
lengthy one. We basically want to go
长。 我们基本上是想
ahead and remove male female lead. Then
彻底取消男女主角的设定。 然后
we're going to change it to Marot
我们要把它改成 Marot，
because this one is just going to be of
因为这张照片就只有
her. And then for the Deadpool one, you
她一个人。 至于死侍，你
can create an element if you want, but
可以根据需要添加一些元素，但
again Deadpool is quite an iconic
死侍是一个非常标志性的
character and he's going to be in his
角色，他会穿着他
usual outfit. So we're just going to say
标志性的服装。 所以我们就直接说“
at Deadpool. and Cling has a very good
死侍”吧。 而且 Cling 对
reference of characters and all of that.
人物塑造等方面都有非常好的参考资料。
So, it works perfectly in this scenario.
所以，在这种情况下，它完全适用。
But now we need to go ahead and finish
但现在我们需要继续完成
off with the timings. So, I basically
时间安排。 所以，我基本上
added this entire script into chat GPT
把整个脚本添加到聊天 GPT 中，
and I said, "How long do you think each
然后问：“你认为每句话会有多长
sentence will be?" And it basically told
？” 它基本上告诉
me 4 seconds for the first sentence, 3
我第一句话 4 秒，
seconds for the second shot, and then 2
第二个镜头 3 秒，
seconds for the final shot. Then we can
最后一个镜头 2 秒。 然后我们就可以
go ahead and hit on generate. And boom.
点击生成了。 砰！
Okay, so now let's quickly jump into a
好的，现在让我们快速了解一下其他
few more workflow scenarios. So let's
几个工作流程场景。
say that we want to create something
假设我们想创建一个
fairly simple like a Deadpool hook. So
像死侍钩子那样简单的东西。 所以
we're going to head over to images, then
我们要进入图像设置，然后选择
Nano Banana Pro, and then we'll go ahead
Nano Banana Pro，接下来我们将
and generate an image of Deadpool. So I
生成一张死侍的图片。 所以我
created this really cool one. And here
创作了这个非常酷的作品。 在这里
you can see the prompt that we used for
你可以看到我们为此使用的提示
this, and it's quite lengthy, but we
，它相当长，但我们
basically just also used this reference
基本上也使用了这张参考
image, [music] and it's a pretty blurry
图片[音乐]，它相当模糊
one, and the results are actually pretty
，但结果实际上非常
incredible. So once we got this image,
惊人。 得到这张图片后，
we can go ahead and click on animate.
我们就可以点击“动画”按钮了。
Make sure that we are on cling 3.0 and
确保我们使用的是 Cling 3.0，
then we can disable multi-shots and then
然后我们可以禁用多重拍摄，然后
just do something super simple like
做一些非常简单的事情，比如
manben sound look into the camera and
Manben Sound 看着镜头
says all right listen up dummies because
说：好了，听着，笨蛋们，因为
this is how movies get made now. We can
现在电影就是这样拍出来的。 我们可以
go ahead and hit on generate and it
点击生成按钮，它会生成
gives us this video.
这个视频。
&gt;&gt; All right, listen up dummies because
好了，各位笨蛋，都给我听好了，
this is how movies get made now. Now,
现在电影就是这样拍出来的。 这当然
that's great and all, but that's a
很好，但这只是一个
fairly simple scene. But if you do want
相当简单的场景。 但是，如果您确实
to achieve the most realistic scenes
想要实现最逼真、最
with actual realism and consistency, you
真实且一致的场景，那么您
really do need to be using elements. So,
确实需要使用元素。 所以，
on screen, you can see an example of a
在屏幕上，你可以看到一个
video with just a first frame. And the
只有第一帧的视频示例。
one on the right is using a first frame
右边的那个使用了第一帧
and elements. And you can see that the
和元素。 你可以看到，
camera movement is way more realistic
镜头运动更加逼真，
and it looks like it was actually shot
看起来就像是
on a camera. And of course, that's
用摄像机实际拍摄的一样。 当然，这是
because Cling has a lot more data to
因为 Cling 拥有更多的数据可供
work with. So, it can recreate real
处理。 因此，它可以
camera movements much easier. And like I
更轻松地重现真实的相机运动。 正如我
showed you previously, creating elements
之前向你展示的那样，创建元素
can be a pretty lengthy process,
可能是一个相当漫长的过程，
especially if you're doing this for
特别是如果你要为生成的每个视频都这样做的话
generating. But remember that I did show
。 但请记住，我刚才已经向
you this really awesome feature inside
您展示了应用程序中这个非常棒的功能
of the apps right here. Go ahead and
。 请随意
upload any image. Click on generate from
上传图片。 点击从
12x angles. And then you'll get a bunch
12 个角度生成。 这样你就能看到很多
of different angles, which is awesome.
不同的角度，这太棒了。
Now, quickly to help out with prompting,
现在，为了快速提供一些提示，
if you don't really know what you're
如果您不太清楚自己在
doing or you want a little bit of help,
做什么，或者想要一些帮助，
here are my best practices. Head over to
以下是我的一些最佳实践。 前往
chat GPT. Then, we're going to go ahead
GPT 聊天室。 接下来，我们将
and click on explore GPTs. And the first
点击“探索 GPT”。
one that we're going to be doing is for
我们首先要做的是
[music] images. So, what we're going to
（音乐）图像。 所以，
go ahead and do is basically just type
接下来我们要做的就是直接
in Nano Banana Pro. And the one that
输入 Nano Banana Pro。
I've been using probably last few months
我最近几个月一直在用的就是
is specifically this one. And I will
这个。 我会在
leave a link in the description down
下面的描述中留下链接，方便
below so you can go ahead and access it.
您访问。
But here are a few examples of how I
但以下是我
actually go ahead and use it. So I found
实际使用它的一些例子。 所以我找到了
this reference image, [music] which is
这张参考图片，[音乐]，就是
the one that we used for Margot Robbie,
我们用来拍摄玛格特·罗比的那张，
and I just said, "Give me a prompt
然后我说：“给我一个提示，重新
recreate this exact same image, but
创作这张一模一样的图片，但
change the woman to Margot Robbie." It
把女人换成玛格特·罗比。” 它
breaks it down really well. Like it
解释得非常清楚。 它就像
gives you cinematic stuff, your
电影道具一样，为你提供
wardrobe, your top frame, your
服装、画面、
environment, your lighting, your camera
环境、灯光、
lens, [music] and your style. And it's
镜头、音乐和风格。
really awesome. Again, if we wanted to
真是太棒了。 如果我们想
go ahead and create something a little
创作一些
bit different, again, we have this image
不同的东西，那么，我们这里就有这张图片
right here. Here I say I have an image
。 我在这里说我有一张图片，
but I want to make a similar image but
但我想制作一张类似的图片，但
replace a man of Tom Holland as
把男人换成汤姆·霍兰德扮演的
Spider-Man and a woman as Zena and then
蜘蛛侠，女人换成泽娜，然后
two kids as mini for Chris Hemsworth and
两个孩子分别扮演迷你版的克里斯·海姆斯沃斯，
a girl kid can be like Scarlett
一个女孩可以扮演斯嘉丽·
Johansson. And then you can see here we
约翰逊。 然后您可以看到这里我们
have our entire prompt. Replace the
展示了完整的提示信息。 换掉
adult, replace the adult, replace a
成年人，换掉成年人，换掉
young boy, replace a young girl. [music]
小男孩，换掉小女孩。  [音乐]
And then it describes the environment
然后它描述了环境
and the camera angle which is awesome.
和拍摄角度，非常棒。   在
Here you can see that I wanted a little
这里你可以看到，我想要一张比
this image I generated just using text
我用文本
to image. And then it goes ahead and
转图像功能生成的图像更逼真一些的图像。 然后它就真的这么做了
does that. Gives us this awesome prompt.
。 它给了我们这个很棒的提示。
Again, if you want to restyle stuff, got
再说一遍，如果你想重新设计一些东西，比如
this image, restyle it to a normal man.
这张图，把它重新设计成一个正常的男人。
And then we can use Nelly Banana with a
然后我们可以使用 Nelly Banana 和
reference image to then recreate it
参考图像，按照
exactly how we want. This one was also a
我们想要的方式将其完全重新创建出来。 这个也
pretty cool one. We basically just
相当不错。 我们只是
wanted to create some different angles.
想从不同的角度进行拍摄。
And we'll explain this a little bit
我们
later on in this video, [music] but you
稍后会在本视频中稍作解释[音乐]，但你
can use this image to basically keep the
可以使用这张图片来保持
composition the same and the man the
构图和人物
same, but then change the background,
不变，然后改变背景，
which is super useful. Now, for video
这非常有用。 现在，对于视频
prompt, you actually want to go ahead
提示，您实际上需要
and use the latest Cling 3.0 prompt
使用最新的 Cling 3.0 提示
generator. We'll leave link to that in
生成器。 我们会把链接放在
description down below. Again, we have
下面的描述里。 我们又看到了
this new image, which is more realistic
这张新图片，它
of the one I just showed you. And we
比我刚才给你们看的图片更真实。 我们
basically say, take this image and mimic
基本上是说，抓住这张图片，模仿
the emotion that the man has, probably
这个人的情绪，可能是在
shouting, and then we're kind of
喊叫，然后我们就可以
describing what I want to say. And then
描述我想表达的意思了。 然后砰的一声
boom, here we have our perfect prompt
，我们就得到了完美的
for Clling. It's super useful. We've
Cling 提示。 它超级实用。 我们
used it a bunch recently, especially
最近多次使用它，尤其是
with the Cling launch, and it's been
在 Cling 产品发布期间，它的表现
really amazing. Now, to finish off, I do
非常出色。 最后，我
want to quickly highlight what I spoke
想快速强调一下我
about at the start of this video, and
在视频开头提到的内容，
that's how you can actually go ahead and
那就是如何重新
relight, swap objects, refframe
打光、交换对象、重新
compositions, and even click your
构图，甚至点击你的
videos. Now, in order to do this, you
视频。 要实现这一点，您
actually need to be using a different
实际上需要使用不同的
Clling model, which is Cling 3.0
Cling 模型，即 Cling 3.0
Omniedit. So again, you can access this
Omniedit。 所以，您可以
by hovering over to your models, then
通过将鼠标悬停在您的模型上，然后
cling, then omniedit right here. Okay.
点击，再点击这里的 OmniEdit 来访问此功能。 好的。
So let's say that we have this video
假设我们
right here, which is pretty cool. But
这里有一段很棒的视频。 但
let's say we want to completely change
假设我们想彻底改变
everything, but keep the character and
一切，但保持角色和
the product the exact same. So we're
产品完全相同。 首先，我们要把
video into here. And then we have two
视频上传到这里。 然后我们就有两种
different options. The first one is just
不同的选择。 第一个只是
prompting it. And the second one is
提示而已。 第二种方法是
using images or elements. But here
使用图像或元素。 但现在
you'll see now that our video is
您可以看到，我们的视频已经
uploaded, it's basically added an at um
上传了，基本上已经添加了一个链接，
here you can actually see the video
您可以在这里看到视频
here. So if we zoom in, you can see that
。 所以如果我们放大画面，就可以看到
it's playing. We can go ahead and delete
它正在播放。 我们可以把它删除
that. And basically we can just type in
。 基本上，我们只需输入“
we restyle at video but change the
重新设计视频，但将
background to be a snowy mountain. Now
背景改为雪山”即可。 现在
we can leave the settings on auto
我们可以将设置设为自动，
because it's basically using these
因为它基本上就是使用这些
settings right here. You can change it
设置。
if you want 1080p. And then we hit
如果你想要 1080p 分辨率，可以更改设置。 然后我们点击
generate. We get this video. Now, that's
生成。 我们收到了这段视频。 这固然
great, but we don't really have much
很好，但我们实际上并没有太多的
customizability. [music]
定制化空间。  [音乐]
So, I'm going to show you another
那么，我将向你们展示另一种
workflow. If we go ahead and duplicate
工作流程。 如果我们复制
this page, then we can head over to
此页面，那么我们就可以前往
image Nano Banana Pro. And then you'll
Nano Banana Pro 图片页面。 然后你会
see that we actually have our base
看到我们实际上有我们的基础
image, uh, which is one of these ones.
图像，呃，就是这些图像中的一个。
I'm not exactly sure which one it is
我不太确定具体是哪一个
specifically. I believe it might be this
。 我觉得可能是这个
one. Um, but then you can see here that
。 嗯，但是您可以看到，这里
we've got this lengthy prompt right
有一个很长的提示
here. And this prompt was curated using
。 这个提示是根据
the nano banana prompt, which is this
纳米香蕉提示精心挑选的，就是这里这个提示
one right here. Use this image as the
。 以这张图片为
base, but keep the composition the same.
基础，但保持构图不变。
Blah blah blah blah, but change the
废话不多说，但请换个
background and now give me backgrounds
背景，现在给我
where I'm on a movie set and also give
一些电影片场的背景，也给
me one where I'm on a battlefield. And
我一些战场的背景。
we scroll down here, we've got version
我们向下滚动，可以看到版本
one, which is the movie set, then
一，也就是电影场景；然后是
version two, which is the background. I
版本二，也就是背景。 我
did also create a few different
还创作了一些不同的
variations. One on a beach, and then one
版本。 一张在沙滩上，一张
on a rooftop. So, if we go ahead and use
在屋顶上。 所以，如果我们要使用
one of these images, I just want to make
这些图片中的一张，我只是想
sure that we're using the correct frame,
确保我们使用的是正确的帧，
but I believe it's this one. We can go
但我相信是这张。 我们可以
ahead and click on download. Then, if we
点击下载了。 然后，如果我们
head back to the Omni, we can then just
回到 Omni，就可以直接
go ahead and drag in this new image. And
拖入这张新图片了。
now we can go ahead and do restyle at
现在我们可以继续对视频进行重新设计，
video with the with the style of at
使其与
image. Now, if we go ahead and click on
图像的样式保持一致。 现在，如果我们点击
generate, it gives us this video. You
生成按钮，就会得到这个视频。 你
can even lock characters and objects, so
甚至可以锁定角色和对象，这样
everything stays consistent, even the
所有内容，包括文本，都能保持一致
text. And again, you can use this exact
。 同样，您可以使用完全相同的
same method to relight, swap objects,
方法来重新打光、交换对象、
refframe compositions, and even clean up
重新构图，甚至清理
your videos. And there we have it.
视频。 就是这样。   就是
That's how you can master Cling 3.0 in a
这样，你可以通过
simple video just like this. Now, if you
这个简单的视频掌握 Cling 3.0。 如果您
did find this helpful, then be sure to
觉得这个视频对您有帮助，请务必点
like this video and subscribe for more
赞并订阅，以便获取更多
awesome AI updates just like this. And
精彩的人工智能更新内容。
of course, you can check out Cling 3.0 O
当然，你也可以在 Hicksfield 上查看 Cling 3.0 O。
over on Hicksfield. We'll leave a link
我们会在
in the description down below and be
下面的描述中留下链接，请
sure to take advantage of their awesome
务必利用他们
discounts at the moment. And again, if
目前的超值折扣。 再次提醒，如果
you want to learn how to master all the
您想学习如何掌握所有
best AI tools, then be sure to check out
最好的AI工具，请务必查看
my AI community down below. I seen the
下面的我的AI社区。 我看过
next one.
下一个了。